Let's take a look at the prospect map.
This is a way of being able to visualize,
uh, different accounts,
different brands, different service lines,
active pipelines, things of that nature. And I'm just going to go through this
video quickly because it's not real data yet.
This is us working through the process of understanding what is needed to be
viewed because what is needed to be viewed changes the data.
The data work that we do, uh, days or,
you know, weeks later. So really hammering this out is,
is a great idea. It's a lean startup principle first.
So let's just look at how this works and then I'll give everybody a
chance to play around with it and provide some feedback on what it's missing
and filters it could do better at. The prospect map is a page that's
going to be found over here on the sidebar of Sourcetree. And then these
cards right here are actually filterable by what we call pills up at the
top. So if you were to click on the customer pill,
you would notice that these things filter down to just the 13 accounts that
are customer type accounts. If you click that lead button,
now it's both of those things. So it's adding up both customer and lead
and showing you ActivePipeline across those two.
Or you can, uh, click one of these and uncheck that pill.
You could also take a look at prospect count. So that's a really cool
feature. Um, you can also look at stage.
So where are they? Is an appointment scheduled?
This is for sales. Are they a qualified lead?
Has a proposal been sent? Are they in negotiation?
Did we, did the deal close one or close loss?
So this is going to be HubSpot type data right here.
And then we have teams. So right now it's like hometown.
I have Memphis, NTX, uh,
Enterprise. The, again, we can change whatever the pills say,
but I wanted to show the different dimensions that I was thinking about.
And then, of course, we have sales representative names up here.
You can also drag over here. This is going to be what I thought
to be time series data. So that way you can see how the data
changes over time. You're not just looking at a card that shows you one
thing, you're looking at how the card is changing over time.
Which is really, I love time series better than just point in time.
Because when I look at a number and it says 37,
but I can't see what it used to be, then I don't remember or
have a frame of reference for why 37 is even relevant or important.
Down here on the map, you can, uh,
use your mouse wheel to, uh,
uh, excuse me, zoom in. You and the size of the dot,
I'm going to make it so that it's based on,
um, these are called bubbles. So in a bubble chart,
we'll make it the size of the deal and we can work on colors
and icons. I'd be interested in feedback on this.
If you click one, it's going to open up a sidebar that shows you
much more detail about that dot. So we can click over here and see
all those different details over here off to the side as well.
That's a pretty cool feature. You can also click over here on a single
one and then it'll only show you,
um, and I'm going to uncheck this so we can see more.
There's qualified leads, there's proposal sent,
there's negotiation, there's close one,
close loss. Now, let's say you want to look at closed,
you can hold down alt and click close one and loss and now you
see both of them, right? So alt is a cool trick for that.
And you can also click again and then close one and be able to
see all of them at once. So that's a pretty cool trick.
All the customer, uh, account cards are listed down here below so you can
very quickly, like, move between them and not have to come off the screen
and you get to see everything. And I made this collapsible so that you
can close it and it just widens out here.
There may be some little funny things that we have to go fix,
uh, like how the, actually it seems like it's reloading correctly now.
This all can be configured and changed, but I'm gonna,
I saved the best for last. This is my favorite feature.
Um, this is an AI forward feature,
which means when you look at it, it won't make any sense to a
human why this is cool. But you click on the JSON button,
which stands for Javascript Object Notation.
And when we do that, it opens up a data,
uh, blob. Looks like a mess.
Now, you can open up an AI assistant,
such as Perplexity, or in the case of GreenMark,
you would open up, uh,
the, uh, excuse me, the Claude sidebar add-in,
and then you come over here and say, give me five
insights for this data.
And that's literally it, because instead of having to read the chart,
it's literally reading the data itself.
And that is the best way to give AI a chance to see things.
So I might say something like, who is most likely to close that I
should go after? And because
it's reading all that data, it's gonna tell you which one.
Because it can see it. Without this,
it can't see that because it can see the dots,
but it doesn't see everything. And that's the really cool trick behind this.
This can be really useful for integrating AI into a system,
but not having to build an AI model itself.
You're just showing behind the curtain whenever you need to.
If you have any questions about the prospect map,
Let me know. I'm going to try to keep these videos short,
uh, so that there's one video per feature and we don't cover too many.
And that way we can move the videos around and change them as needed
and, uh, re-, re-record little sections whenever necessary.
Thanks for watching.